{
  "exercises": [
    { "question": "Translate to German: I had Pizza.", "answer": "ich hatte Pizza " },
    { "question": "Translate to German: We had pizza.", "answer": "wir hatten pizza" },
    { "question": "Translate to German: He could cook pasta.", "answer": "er konnte pasta kochen" },
    { "question": "Translate to German: They were students.", "answer": "sie waren studenten" },
    { "question": "Translate to German: She wanted to learn German.", "answer": "sie wollte deutsch lernen" },

   
    { "question": "Translate to German: We had to eat vegetables.", "answer": "wir mussten gemüse essen" },
   
    { "question": "Translate to German: He played football.", "answer": "er spielte fußball" },
    { "question": "Translate to German: They wanted to travel.", "answer": "sie wollten reisen" },

    { "question": "Translate to German: You (informal) had tea.", "answer": "du hattest tee" },
    { "question": "Translate to German: She could speak English.", "answer": "sie konnte englisch sprechen" },
    { "question": "Translate to German: I was tired.", "answer": "ich war müde" },
    { "question": "Translate to German: We should help him.", "answer": "wir sollten ihm helfen" },
    { "question": "Translate to German: He had milk.", "answer": "er hatte milch" },

    
    { "question": "Translate to German: They could play football.", "answer": "sie konnten fußball spielen" },
    { "question": "Translate to German: We were happy.", "answer": "wir waren glücklich" },
    { "question": "Translate to German: You (informal) wanted to eat cake.", "answer": "du wolltest kuchen essen" },
    { "question": "Translate to German: She had to drink water.", "answer": "sie musste wasser trinken" }
  ]
}
